{
    "subject": "Alexandra_Wentworth",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "George_Stephanopoulos",
    "human_readable": "Alexandra Wentworth is married to George Stephanopoulos.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9500999450683594,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Alexandra Wentworth and George Stephanopoulos?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9374462962150574,
            "question": "To whom is Alexandra Wentworth married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9354378581047058,
            "question": "Is Alexandra Wentworth married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8825749754905701,
            "question": "Who is married to George Stephanopoulos?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8708630800247192,
            "question": "Name a famous person who is married to George Stephanopoulos."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8502190709114075,
            "question": "Is George Stephanopoulos married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7845216989517212,
            "question": "Name a spouse of George Stephanopoulos."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.783543586730957,
            "question": "Who is Alexandra Wentworth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6371301412582397,
            "question": "Who shares a marital relationship with George Stephanopoulos?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6167355179786682,
            "question": "What is the name of George Stephanopoulos's spouse?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Alexandra Wentworth is married to George Stephanopoulos.",
            "html": "yago_3650_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who shares a marital relationship with George Stephanopoulos?",
            "html": "yago_3650_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Alexandra Wentworth?",
            "html": "yago_3650_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a spouse of George Stephanopoulos.",
            "html": "yago_3650_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_3650_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_3650_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_3650_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_3650_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_3650_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_3650_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_3650_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_3650_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_3650_90.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_3650_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format for your query:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. There are multiple mentions of Ali Wentworth being married to George Stephanopoulos, including their wedding date (November 20, 2001), the fact that they have two daughters together, and that they have been married for over a decade."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly state that George Stephanopoulos is married to Ali Wentworth, confirming the statement that Alexandra (\"Ali\") Wentworth is married to George Stephanopoulos."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}